parveentravels.com 2006-09-05

# PRIVACY POLICY - Parveen Travels (P) Ltd.

Parveen Travels respects the privacy of visitors to our site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices for our Thokalath.com site. Questions regarding privacy issues should be directed to parveen@parveentravels.com 

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We won't knowingly allow anyone under 14 to provide any other personally identifying information. 

The information gathered by Parveen Travels on this site falls into two categories: 

  * Information voluntarily supplied by visitors to our site when they request information about Parveen Travels 
  * Non personally-identifiable information about our visitors's connection to the Internet collected by our servers. 

Our site allows visitors to submit contact information in order to receive information, to be added to or deleted from our mailing list/fax list, and to request additional information. When visitors submit such information to Parveen Travels through this site, Parveen Travels will use this information only to provide the requested information and services. Individuals within Parveen Travels who have a need to view the information will have access to the information submitted by visitors to this site. 

In addition, our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our sites. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally to us. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to measure traffic within our site, and to tailor specific information to certain general classes of IP addresses. 

We may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Visitor Agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our site, the public, or Parveen Travels. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that Parveen Travels, the bulk of our assets or our site is acquired by another company, information relating to our visitors would be among the transferred assets.

**A final note:**  
The Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we'll post the changes before they take effect. By visiting our site, you agree that your visit, and any dispute over our privacy practices, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our Visitor Agreement.
